(Amy:)I think we need
to face the cold, hard truth:
(Amy:)I was sexually aroused
by Penny's friend Zack.
(Sheldon:)Hang on. I don't know
(Sheldon:)that we've given
the alien parasite hypothesis
(Sheldon:)a fair shake.
(Amy:)Let's look at this logically.
I have a stomach; I get hungry.
I have genitals; I have the
potential for sexual arousal.
(Sheldon:)A cross we all must bear.
(Sheldon:)You know, in difficult
moments like this,
(Sheldon:)I often turn to a force
greater than myself.
(Amy:)Religion?
Star Trek.
Did you see
Star Trek: The Motion Picture?
(Leonard:)No.
Don't. It's terrible. However...
(Sheldon:)in it, we learn that
(Sheldon:)when Spock finds himself
drawn off the path of logic
(Sheldon:)by feelings bubbling up from his
human half, he suppresses them
(Sheldon:)using the Vulcan mental
discipline of Kolinar.
(Amy:)Are you suggesting
we live our lives
(Amy:)guided by the philosophies
found in cheap science fiction?
"Cheap science fiction"?